<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>golang on Blanton Technology</title>
    <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/tags/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in golang on Blanton Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 23:01:34 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http:///blantontechnology.com/tags/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Prometheus Metrics Exporter for ZFS</title>
      <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/2020/creating-a-prometheus-metrics-exporter-for-zfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 23:01:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:///blantontechnology.com/2020/creating-a-prometheus-metrics-exporter-for-zfs/</guid>
      <description>Creating a Prometheus Exporter for Proxmox ZFS I&amp;rsquo;m starting to get into monitoring with Prometheus and Alertmanager. One of the first things I want to start monitoring is ZFS on my Proxmox server. I noticed that there isn&amp;rsquo;t many exporters to scrape ZFS information so I decided to figure out how to create an exporter that can I can then use to monitor my ZFS zpools.
The source code for the end result is here: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Kubernetes Controller</title>
      <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/2020/creating-a-kubernetes-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 02:23:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:///blantontechnology.com/2020/creating-a-kubernetes-controller/</guid>
      <description>Creating a Kubernetes Controller Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get deeper into Kubernetes whether I&amp;rsquo;m learning best practices or trying to develop tools on and for the platform. This lead me down the road to learning how to create a controller for Kubernetes. Turns out, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t a very smooth road.
The current implementation for the controller is located at https://github.com/zbblanton/cloudflare_dynamic_dns_controller.
The Goal I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to build a controller for Kubernetes that runs in the cluster but didn&amp;rsquo;t have any ideas until I thought of doing some simple dynamic DNS for Cloudflare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Cloudflare Dynamic Dns on Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/setting-up-cloudflare-dynamic-dns-on-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 05:03:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/setting-up-cloudflare-dynamic-dns-on-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Cloudflare Dynamic DNS On Kubernetes I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on switching all of my home infrastructure to Kubernetes including the blog you&amp;rsquo;re reading now. My ISP luckily doesn&amp;rsquo;t block port 80 and 443 so I can simply let Cloudflare point to my public IP. The problem is my IP is dynamic and can change at any point. So I needed something that can watch for my IP to change and then update Cloudflare with the new address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Web Server on OpenFaaS</title>
      <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/building-a-web-server-on-openfaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 04:02:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/building-a-web-server-on-openfaas/</guid>
      <description>Building a Web Server on OpenFaaS Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing around with OpenFaaS on Kubernetes and I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for a small project to run on it. I&amp;rsquo;ve also wanted to start this static blog and figured this is a perfect project to run on OpenFaaS.
Prerequisites Before we start make sure you have installed OpenFaaS on Kubernetes. This can be done in a few commands if you already have Helm installed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
