<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloudflare on Blanton Technology</title>
    <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/tags/cloudflare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloudflare on Blanton Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 21:16:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http:///blantontechnology.com/tags/cloudflare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Jenkins Pipeline for the Blog</title>
      <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/building-a-jenkins-pipeline-for-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 21:16:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/building-a-jenkins-pipeline-for-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>Building a Jenkins Pipeline for the Blog Currently it&amp;rsquo;s a pain to publish posts or edit this blog. I develop the blog locally with the built in web server that comes with Hugo. Then once I&amp;rsquo;m done making a post or modifying the site I run hugo and it compiles all my markdown into HTML. Once compiled I push my site to GitHub. From this point I have to manually pull the repo down, build a new docker image, push it, then deploy the new image as a function on OpenFaaS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Cloudflare Dynamic Dns on Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/setting-up-cloudflare-dynamic-dns-on-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 05:03:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http:///blantontechnology.com/2019/setting-up-cloudflare-dynamic-dns-on-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Cloudflare Dynamic DNS On Kubernetes I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on switching all of my home infrastructure to Kubernetes including the blog you&amp;rsquo;re reading now. My ISP luckily doesn&amp;rsquo;t block port 80 and 443 so I can simply let Cloudflare point to my public IP. The problem is my IP is dynamic and can change at any point. So I needed something that can watch for my IP to change and then update Cloudflare with the new address.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
